Fenerbahce continues to make significant changes in the squad and add new abilities.
Yellow-lacivertliler, accelerating the transfer work by accelerating a young and promising name to the squad: Senegalli 18-year-old Abdu Aziz Foll.
Foll, which has been shown as one of the important potentials of Senegal football recently, will sweat for the jersey.
If you are ready, our 100 -second video will start to get to know Abdu Aziz Foll.
Abdu Aziz Foll was born on February 20, 2007 in Senegal.
Aziz, who started football on the streets, was discovered by the scouts of the Madiyor Club in his village thanks to his talent and transferred to the club's infrastructure at the age of 15.
The coaches started to assign him directly in the midfield with the U17 team.
In his jerseys, he began to use his name Aziz.
The most talked about thing about the young actor who quickly adapted to the squad was maturity and an exemplary personality.
Soon the captain was caught in his arm, and he did not frustrate his trust.
In 2020, the A level rose to the level.
In the same year, the U17 fought for Senegal in the African Cup Cup and became one of the captains of the team.
The tournament resulted in the championship.
South Africa match in the quarter -finals a little ineffective, the semi -final Burkina Faso match scored a goal.
He became one of the remarkable names of the tournament and also managed to be elected to the top 11 of the tournament.
Comments on him in the country's press were that it would be an important midfielder in the future.
The young talent, which was shown as the balance element of the team, was considered one of the indispensables of the first 11.
Foll, who was selected as the player of the match against Somalik, said that he had given his award to the people of Senegal.
The teachers he worked for, "a very serious player compared to his age.
Working with his determination and personality.
He's always a footballer who wants to do his best.
The performance needs to satisfy himself first," he uses.
Foll continued to make a name for himself in his country, he was transferred to SMA in February 2025.
For him, a new gate of honor was opened: Fenerbahce.
Yellow-lacivertlilerin scouts after liked the player presented to the technical committee.
The player who received full marks from the technical committee, thus signed the contract connecting him to Fenerbahce.
In a statement made by the club, a 5 -year -old contract was signed with the 18 -year -old player.
Among the prominent features of Aziz, long length and speed stand out.
Foll, which is also effective in the role of cutter, draws attention with its ability to finish the fast attacks on the right before starting.
The young player, who is known as the "Box-to-Box" man in his team, is of particular importance with his skills to manage game.
Foll, one of the most running names in the field and is one of the most trapped names, is a player who loves to go upright with the ball.
The fact that it triggers aggression and attack is also written as a plus to its household.
As Foll's cons, we can count the immaturity of his young age.
The fact that he is not very experienced at A team level yet and that he could not show himself in high competitive tournaments is a question mark for him.
However, all this can be considered as normal reactions to be given at this age.
Because Abdu Aziz Foll is an investment made for the future rather than today.
So how do you evaluate this transfer.
What do you think about the transfers of Fenerbahçe's young player.
We are waiting for your comments.
This place is short pass, goodbye.